[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Syria", "Iran"]}, "docId": "130903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "MD", "VBD", "DT", "TO", "PRP", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 47, "question": "What do you say to that argument?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "to", "that", "argument", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 48, "answer": "Well I'd said this to him today, is that I do think that Syria and Iran for instance are very different circumstances.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "I", "'d", "said", "this", "to", "him", "today", ",", "is", "that", "I", "do", "think", "that", "Syria", "and", "Iran", "for", "instance", "are", "very", "different", "circumstances", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WP", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 56, "question": "Are you on board at least with the United States supplying arms to the rebels?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "on", "board", "at", "least", "with", "the", "United", "States", "supplying", "arms", "to", "the", "rebels", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "IN", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", "VBG", "NNS", "TO", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 57, "answer": "Well, I'm not in part because I still don't think we have a good hand on who the rebels are.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "in", "part", "because", "I", "still", "do", "n't", "think", "we", "have", "a", "good", "hand", "on", "who", "the", "rebels", "are", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["United States"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "JJR", "RB", "CC", "VBN", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "CC", "VBN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "First of all Congressman King, what do you make of this draft resolution that the Senate Foreign Relations Committee has come up with giving the President the authority to strike in a limited way over the next 60 days with an option of adding another 30 days if necessary?", "question_tokens": ["First", "of", "all", "Congressman", "King", ",", "what", "do", "you", "make", "of", "this", "draft", "resolution", "that", "the", "Senate", "Foreign", "Relations", "Committee", "has", "come", "up", "with", "giving", "the", "President", "the", "authority", "to", "strike", "in", "a", "limited", "way", "over", "the", "next", "60", "days", "with", "an", "option", "of", "adding", "another", "30", "days", "if", "necessary", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "Yes, I have to look at it more carefully but based on what I've heard and seen tonight, I would vote for it.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "have", "to", "look", "at", "it", "more", "carefully", "but", "based", "on", "what", "I", "'ve", "heard", "and", "seen", "tonight", ",", "I", "would", "vote", "for", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congressman King", "Senate Foreign Relations Committee"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBN", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 78, "question": "Would you vote for this resolution?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "vote", "for", "this", "resolution", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 79, "answer": "Well, I think the said language is certainly a step in the right direction.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "the", "said", "language", "is", "certainly", "a", "step", "in", "the", "right", "direction", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last 30", "1950s"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"], "PERSON": ["Reagan", "Clinton", "Eisenhower"]}, "docId": "130903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBG", "RB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CD", ",", "CD", "NNS", "RB", "DT", "NN", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "NNP", ":", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "CD", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "VB", "RB", "TO", "DT", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 88, "question": "You would've wanted him just to use his executive authority and get the job done without Congress, is that right?", "question_tokens": ["You", "would", "'ve", "wanted", "him", "just", "to", "use", "his", "executive", "authority", "and", "get", "the", "job", "done", "without", "Congress", ",", "is", "that", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "CC", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 89, "answer": "Well, going back over the last 30, 40 years almost every instance such as this presidents have acted without going to Congress; President Reagan, President Clinton they acted six times, he carried out bombing attacks during his presidency, President Eisenhower go back to the 1950s.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "going", "back", "over", "the", "last", "30", ",", "40", "years", "almost", "every", "instance", "such", "as", "this", "presidents", "have", "acted", "without", "going", "to", "Congress", ";", "President", "Reagan", ",", "President", "Clinton", "they", "acted", "six", "times", ",", "he", "carried", "out", "bombing", "attacks", "during", "his", "presidency", ",", "President", "Eisenhower", "go", "back", "to", "the", "1950s", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "."], "qSentId": 99, "question": "Congressman Schiff, you want to respond to that?", "question_tokens": ["Congressman", "Schiff", ",", "you", "want", "to", "respond", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 100, "answer": "I do.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Schiff"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 134, "question": "How significant, Congressman King, is the Rand Paul wing now with the Republican Party who basically want to stay out of these Foreign Affairs?", "question_tokens": ["How", "significant", ",", "Congressman", "King", ",", "is", "the", "Rand", "Paul", "wing", "now", "with", "the", "Republican", "Party", "who", "basically", "want", "to", "stay", "out", "of", "these", "Foreign", "Affairs", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "WP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 135, "answer": "I think it's excruciatingly dangerous isolation's wing in the party.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "it", "'s", "excruciatingly", "dangerous", "isolation", "'s", "wing", "in", "the", "party", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congressman King", "Rand Paul", "Republican Party"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "When you hear that, as a military man, what does that say to you?", "question_tokens": ["When", "you", "hear", "that", ",", "as", "a", "military", "man", ",", "what", "does", "that", "say", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "IN", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "I think that authorizes him to conduct any kind of covert action he'd like to use.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "authorizes", "him", "to", "conduct", "any", "kind", "of", "covert", "action", "he", "'d", "like", "to", "use", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 198, "question": "Now, that's a possibility isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["Now", ",", "that", "'s", "a", "possibility", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 199, "answer": "Well, that's always the concern.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "always", "the", "concern", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "POS", "NN", "NNS", "WDT", "VBD", "NN", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 203, "question": "When the language in the resolution says that it will be a limited and tailored operation designed to deter serious use of these kinds of weapons and to degrade Syria's capacity to use such weapons in the future, explained from the military perspective what that suggests to you?", "question_tokens": ["When", "the", "language", "in", "the", "resolution", "says", "that", "it", "will", "be", "a", "limited", "and", "tailored", "operation", "designed", "to", "deter", "serious", "use", "of", "these", "kinds", "of", "weapons", "and", "to", "degrade", "Syria", "'s", "capacity", "to", "use", "such", "weapons", "in", "the", "future", ",", "explained", "from", "the", "military", "perspective", "what", "that", "suggests", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "VBN", "CC", "VBN", "NN", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNS", "CC", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "IN", "VBZ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 204, "answer": "Well that's a very difficult passage because I think the chances of going after the chemical weapon's delivery systems which were rocket launchers and he's got thousands of them all over the country.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", "that", "'s", "a", "very", "difficult", "passage", "because", "I", "think", "the", "chances", "of", "going", "after", "the", "chemical", "weapon", "'s", "delivery", "systems", "which", "were", "rocket", "launchers", "and", "he", "'s", "got", "thousands", "of", "them", "all", "over", "the", "country", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Syria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "DT", "IN", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "RB", "IN", "PRP", ":"], "qSentId": 227, "question": "I think you've got a chance to go through it turtle (ph) pass in the Foreign Relations Committee almost certainly will pass in the senate but what does it say to you?", "question_tokens": ["I", "think", "you", "'ve", "got", "a", "chance", "to", "go", "through", "it", "turtle", "(", "ph", ")", "pass", "in", "the", "Foreign", "Relations", "Committee", "almost", "certainly", "will", "pass", "in", "the", "senate", "but", "what", "does", "it", "say", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "PRP", "RB", ":", "NN", ":", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "RB", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 228, "answer": "You know I'm not in favor of the resolution both in principle and in the specifics, well if I --", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", "I", "'m", "not", "in", "favor", "of", "the", "resolution", "both", "in", "principle", "and", "in", "the", "specifics", ",", "well", "if", "I", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Foreign Relations Committee"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NNP", "VBD", "DT", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 229, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 230, "answer": "Well, the President had all the authority he needed.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "President", "had", "all", "the", "authority", "he", "needed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Wolf"]}, "docId": "130903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 281, "question": "Richard, what happened to the coalition, the huge coalition that the US would normally like to get involved at another Arab country like Syria?", "question_tokens": ["Richard", ",", "what", "happened", "to", "the", "coalition", ",", "the", "huge", "coalition", "that", "the", "US", "would", "normally", "like", "to", "get", "involved", "at", "another", "Arab", "country", "like", "Syria", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "DT", "NNP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 282, "answer": "Well, the short answer, as you know, Wolf, is it's not going to happen.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "short", "answer", ",", "as", "you", "know", ",", "Wolf", ",", "is", "it", "'s", "not", "going", "to", "happen", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["US", "Syria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 292, "question": "How much of what President Obama is doing right now is designed not just to send the signal to Syria but to really send a signal to Iran?", "question_tokens": ["How", "much", "of", "what", "President", "Obama", "is", "doing", "right", "now", "is", "designed", "not", "just", "to", "send", "the", "signal", "to", "Syria", "but", "to", "really", "send", "a", "signal", "to", "Iran", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "IN", "WP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "TO", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 293, "answer": "Very much.", "answer_tokens": ["Very", "much", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"], "LOCATION": ["Syria", "Iran"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "EX", "VBZ", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 305, "question": "Are you surprised it has taken so long for the world to wake up to the horror of what's going on in Syria?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "surprised", "it", "has", "taken", "so", "long", "for", "the", "world", "to", "wake", "up", "to", "the", "horror", "of", "what", "'s", "going", "on", "in", "Syria", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 306, "answer": "Look, there's always been a degree of selective response to these humanitarian crises.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "there", "'s", "always", "been", "a", "degree", "of", "selective", "response", "to", "these", "humanitarian", "crises", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Syria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "WP", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 325, "question": "When he sees this debate unfolding in the United States, how worried should he really be that he's about to get crashed if you will by US Tomahawk cruise missiles?", "question_tokens": ["When", "he", "sees", "this", "debate", "unfolding", "in", "the", "United", "States", ",", "how", "worried", "should", "he", "really", "be", "that", "he", "'s", "about", "to", "get", "crashed", "if", "you", "will", "by", "US", "Tomahawk", "cruise", "missiles", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNPS", ",", "WRB", "VBN", "MD", "PRP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "Well, I'm not sure I completely understand what he's thinking right now.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "sure", "I", "completely", "understand", "what", "he", "'s", "thinking", "right", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["US Tomahawk"], "LOCATION": ["United States"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 360, "question": "Is he another Hitler?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "another", "Hitler", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 361, "answer": "No, I don't think so.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "VBZ", "TO", "RB", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 389, "question": "How do you think the American news media is doing right now in the buildup what could be an escalation of the US military involvement in Syria?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "think", "the", "American", "news", "media", "is", "doing", "right", "now", "in", "the", "buildup", "what", "could", "be", "an", "escalation", "of", "the", "US", "military", "involvement", "in", "Syria", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NNS", "VBZ", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 390, "answer": "Well, one of the things that the media tries to do is to simply survive.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "one", "of", "the", "things", "that", "the", "media", "tries", "to", "do", "is", "to", "simply", "survive", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["US", "Syria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 399, "question": "And David, if Bashar al-Assad were to fall -- no indication he's about to fall any time soon -- but if he were to fall, is there a possibility that Al-Qaeda could emerge as the new leadership of Syria?", "question_tokens": ["And", "David", ",", "if", "Bashar", "al-Assad", "were", "to", "fall", "--", "no", "indication", "he", "'s", "about", "to", "fall", "any", "time", "soon", "--", "but", "if", "he", "were", "to", "fall", ",", "is", "there", "a", "possibility", "that", "Al-Qaeda", "could", "emerge", "as", "the", "new", "leadership", "of", "Syria", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", ":", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "RB", ":", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "EX", "DT", "NN", "WDT", "-NONE-", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 400, "answer": "I don't think right now.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "think", "right", "now", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["David"], "LOCATION": ["Syria"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "IN", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "Now, first of all, what's your most vivid memory of the rubble at the World Trade Center on 9/11 because you were there and that flag certainly became a symbol?", "question_tokens": ["Now", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "what", "'s", "your", "most", "vivid", "memory", "of", "the", "rubble", "at", "the", "World", "Trade", "Center", "on", "9/11", "because", "you", "were", "there", "and", "that", "flag", "certainly", "became", "a", "symbol", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "WDT", "POS", "PRP$", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "CC", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "It was the enormity of I think -- when we got there, you know, I came back that night and just started to see the people that were trying to help us with buckets.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "was", "the", "enormity", "of", "I", "think", "--", "when", "we", "got", "there", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "came", "back", "that", "night", "and", "just", "started", "to", "see", "the", "people", "that", "were", "trying", "to", "help", "us", "with", "buckets", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 442, "question": "What made that photos the most iconic image, shall we say, the memory of that tragic day in 2001?", "question_tokens": ["What", "made", "that", "photos", "the", "most", "iconic", "image", ",", "shall", "we", "say", ",", "the", "memory", "of", "that", "tragic", "day", "in", "2001", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBN", "IN", "NNS", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 443, "answer": "Well, you know, everybody was looking for the hope.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "everybody", "was", "looking", "for", "the", "hope", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["2001"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130903pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "NN", "PRP", "RP", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 450, "question": "Where was that real flag?", "question_tokens": ["Where", "was", "that", "real", "flag", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBD", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 451, "answer": "Well, you know, we'll never know I guess unless you guys figure it out, and you're going to tell us tomorrow.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "we", "'ll", "never", "know", "I", "guess", "unless", "you", "guys", "figure", "it", "out", ",", "and", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "tell", "us", "tomorrow", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]